<main_material>
	Celestial Steel - 			Makai_Ingot
	Stardust - 				Makai_Stardust 				<desc>placbo universal fuel</desc>
	Celestial Fabric - 			Makai_Fabric_C		<notdone> 	<desc>a piece of fabric originate from Makai, also known as Star Cradle. extremely high heat resist. immune even. one of the needed material to create Primodial Forge. Thing made from Celestial Fabric will never burn.</desc>
	Flame of the First Forge - 		Makai_Forge_Flame 	<notdone> 	<desc>endgame item. a universal fuel althought not all building can utilize it full power efficiently. mostly non-makai building.
		<source>Primodial Forge</source>

<Building>
	</>Makai Interdimensional Relay - 	Makai_Bench
	</>Celestial Wall - 			MakainiumWall
	</>Makai Interdimensional Uplink - 	Makai_Powerlink_Relay 		<desc>research bench linkable</desc>
	</>Stardust-particle accelerator - 	Makai_Turret_A
	<X>Stardust-beam compresser -		Makai_Turret_B
	<X>Interdimension Receiver - 		Makai_En_Reciever		<desc>recieve raw energy from Makai</desc>
	<X>Makai Energy Converter - 		Makai_En_Condens		<desc>convert raw energy into usable power. in a form of raw star particle</desc>
	<X>Stardust Particle Collecter -	Makai_St_Conv			<desc>convert star particle into Stardust</desc>
	<X>Celestial Steel Forge -		Makai_Cs_Forg			<desc>convert star particle into Celestial Steel</desc> 
	
	<X>Primodial Forge -			Makai_PForge		<desc>a forge created in the image of The First Forge, and inherit part of it power. it had forged a foundation for all thing that exist. and that yet to exist. those who control the Primodial Forge, control the very foundation of the universe. \n your colony has come far to reach this point. only thing limiting you at this point is the pawn own imagination. any material can be forged here, even those that yet to exist in our world. \n\n Think of this forge as a source of infinite resource, support quite a few modden material(more can be added based on request)</desc> 
	
	
<Branching_Material> - needed to make Primodial Forge
	Essence of Corruption - 	Makai_C-Path_E 		<notdone> Insanity related item
	Essence of Bond - 		Makai_B-Path_E 		<notdone> Social boost related item
	Essence of Fate - 		Makai_F-Path_E 		<notdone> Healing related item
	Essence of Knowledge -		Makai_K-Path_E 		<notdone> Research speed boost
	Essence of Frost -		Makai_Fr-Path_E		<notdone> temperature control building. cold
	Essence of Flame		Makai_Fla-Path_E	<notdone> temperature control building. hot
	Essence of Existence - 		Makai_E-Path_E		<notdone> IDM. self healing speed.
	Essence of Destruction- 	Makai_D-Path_E		<notdone> mitigate enemies defense. and increase their IDM.
	Essence of Order - 		Makai_Or-Path_E		<notdone> keep thing tidy. reduce mental break threshold. Slave no longer rebel. increase psyfocus gain.
	Essence of Death - 		Makai_Dea-Path_E	<notdone> Deadly 13th. a countdown hediff that will kill a pawn in 13 days.
	Essence of Distortion - 	Makai_Dis-Path_E	<notdone> undecided.

	
	Essence of Beyond -		Makai_SNS-Path_E	<notdone> SNS compat support. crafted from 1_Eternium 1_Stable Matter
	Essence of Archotech - 		Makai_MAG-Path_E	<notdone> More Archotech Garbage patch. crafted with 250 ArchoMass and 25 ArchoFragment
	Essence of Glitter - 		Makai_GT-Path_E		<notdone> Glitter Tech patch. crafted with 100 Alpha Poly and 100 Beta Poly.
	Essence of Infinity -		Makai_Ducks-Path_E	<notdone> Duck's Insane skill patch. require pawn with 25 or more crafting to craft
	Essence of The Deep -		Makai_Moyo-Path_E	<notdone> Moyo-From the depth patch. require 500 Abyssal Steel to craft
	Essence of Warfare -		Makai_VFEM-Path_E	<notdone> Vanilla Faction Expanded Mechanoid patch. require 100 Mechanoid Component to craft.
	Essence of Desire -		Makai_De-Path_E		<notdone> Simple Warrant patch. no, you don't get to warrant for all other essence for cheap. now pay up. this one cost 10k silver. (100k if any of the infinite resource mod is active. including Mines2.0/Planetary Drill/Omni Core Drill
	Essence of Lust	- 		Makai_RJW-Path_E	<notdone> RJW patch. not required to make the forge, basically a reskinned fertility pill. you WILL have more kids. 

<Item ParentName="Corruption">
	Collapsed Will - Melee weapon,Claw shape,each hit give a build-up hediff. max sev = go berserk
	Pillar of maddness - a pillar with 5x5 maddness radius. *warning* affect ally.

<Item ParentName="Bond">
	Ring of bond - wearer gain increased social boost.
	Pillar of communication - 5x5 radius social boost.

<Item ParentName="Fate">
	Convergence of Fate - Building that give immunity gain speed and injury healing speed.
	Droplet of miracle - Consumable, massive boost to healing and immunity gain speed in a short amount of time.(5s)

<Item ParentName="Knowledge">
	Varia Bracelet - Increase research speed and learning speed. some boost to global work speed.	<done>
	Knowledge Seeker - Bow that increase user learning speed. precise aim.	<done>
	
<Item ParentName="Frost">
	Frigid Star	- Staff weapon. considered as ranged. shoot cold orb that inflic hyperthemia and unique debuff.
	Cold Slumber - a building that cool down room. give hypothemia hediff in a 2x2 radius, plan carefully.
	
<Item ParentName="Flame">
	Sunblade - Flame sword. deal heat damage. make user immune to heat. can shoot fireball
	Passioned Flame - a building that heat up room. give heatstroke hediff in 2x2 radius, plan carefully.
	
<Item ParentName="Existence">
	Existence(the weapon) - Halberd that give user massive boost to healing ability. reduce pain they feel.		<done>
	Guidance Light - pillar with 3x3 radius buff range. make pawn take less damage, very expensive.
	
<Item ParentName="Destruction">
	Entity Null - Gigantic sword. shoot lightning. nullify enemies defense. and increase target IDM.	<done>
	Ring of Lightning - a lightning ring that periodically shoot at enemies. give move speed increase.
	
<Item ParentName="Order">
	Order(the weapon) - a big halberd. reduce wearer mental break threshold. increase psyfocus gain. reduce psycast heat gain.
	Ring of Absolute Order - given to slave. 100% Slave Suppression Offset. 
	
<Item ParentName="Death">
	Destined Death - a big scythe. insanely high armor pen. but deal no damage. on hit give a stacking hediff, once reach full severity victim will die in 13 days.
	The Death Reversed - 13 use resurrecter. no drawback <Require More Archotech Garbage>
	
<Item ParentName="Distortion">
	
	
