<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<EssenceOfTheUniverse>

	<!-- order from easiest to hardest to acquire -->
		<note>MFA = Makai Fabrication Altar</note>
	<Essence_Of_Corruption>
		<Method>
			<li>Finish specific research, then craft seed of corruption from Makai Fabrication Altar</li>
			<li>perform operation to plant the seed into pawn brain. take 5 days to growth into Slumbering Essence of Corruption</li>
			<li>during the 5 days duration, victim will experience constant berserk.</li>
			<li>once the seed is fully grow. extract it from the pawn(Lethal) to get Essence of Insanity</li>
		</Method>
	</Essence_Of_Corruption>
	
	<Essence_Of_Order>
		<Method>
			<li>Finish specific research.</li>
			<li>similar to Seed of Corruption, plant the base essence inside pawn brain and wait for 5 days</li>
			<li>pawn with seed will experience increase mood boost, gain suppressionPerDay instead of losing(incase of slave) never have mental break.</li>
			<li>after 5 days base essence will grow into Slumbering Essence of Order</li>
		</Method>
	</Essence_Of_Order>
	
	<Essence_Of_Knowledge>
		<Method>
			<li>Finish a 120k point research(it own specific research) then craft 3 Fragment of Knowledge from MFA</li>
			<li>Combine the 3 Fragment of Knowledge into Essence of Knowledge at MFA</li>
		</Method>
	</Essence_Of_Knowledge>
	
	<Essence_of_Flame>
		<Method>
			<li>Finish specific research, then build Essence Consolidator - Flame</li>
			<li>Craft Base Essence of Flame from MFA</li>
			<li>Process it in the machine for 5 days</li>
			<li>in order for machine to work, room need to be in at least 200c or higher</li>
		</Method>
	</Essence_of_Flame>
	
	<Essence_of_Frost>
		<Method>
			<li>Finish specific research, then build Essence Consolidator - Frost</li>
			<li>Craft Base Essence of Frost from MFA</li>
			<li>Process it in the machine for 5 days</li>
			<li>in order for machine to work, room need to be in at least -100c or lower</li>
		</Method>
	</Essence_of_Frost>
	
	<Essence_Of_Death>
		<Method>
			<li>Finish specific research,</li>
			<li>Craft Fragment of Death - First Half at MFA. require 100 corses of any type</li>
			<li>Craft Fragment of Death - Second Half at MFA. require 20 heart</li>
			<li>Harvest 1 Soul from humanlike pawn through operation(Lethal)</li>
		</Method>
	</Essence_Of_Death>
	
	<Essence_Of_Distortion>
		<Method> <!-- May change in the future -->
			<li>Finish specific research</li>
			<li>combine Essence of Order and Corruption</li>
		</Method>
	</Essence_Of_Distortion>
	
	<Essence_Of_Destruction>
		<Method>
			<li>Finish specific research</li>
			<li>combinee Essence of Flame,Death,Corruption</li>
		</Method>
	</Essence_Of_Destruction>
	
	<Essence_Of_Bond>
		<Method>
			<li>Finish specific research</li>
			<li>Craft Base Essence of Bond from MFA</li>
			<li>install into pawn as implant called Warmth of Bond.</li>
			<li>pawn with WoB will emit Bond aura. give nearby pawn a Bond level</li>
			<li>Bond Level increase at minimum once per day. a total of 5 days needed to reach lvl 5</li>
			<li>Once Bond Level reach lvl 5. there will be a new hediff, Bond Fragment.</li>
			<li>Extract at least 2 Bond Fragment and extract base essence to combine into Bond Fragment.</li>
		</Method>
	</Essence_Of_Bond>
	
	<Essence_Of_Fate>
		<Method>
			<li>
			Implant String of Fate into pawn, setMax Consciousness to 1%. 
			over the duration of 5 days will transform each limb and part into Fated [Bodypart_Name] Implant.
			after 5 days has passed, Fated Bodypart will get stronger every 24 hours.
			String of Fate will disappear and replace with Fated Heart and apply Fated Encounter. 
			pawn will be in permanent Berserk for 5 days.
			player have to defeat that pawn without killing. 
			after doing so they have to be keep contained until Fated Encounter reach full severity
			at max severity Fated Encounter no longer give mental break.
			Fated Implant will reach full severity after at least 10 days including the time they spawn in during transformation.
			at max severity Fated Implant will turn into full on Fated Bodypart. after that each Fated Bodypart can be harvest/remove to gain
			Fated Fragment. since there no lung replacement in vanilla there will be a temporary fake lung that cost 5 stardust.
			take all 10 Fated Fragment and craft into 1 Essence of Fate at Makai Altar
			alternatively, player can keep the super pawn without harvesting part.
			</li>
		</Method>
	</Essence_Of_Fate>
	
	<Essence_Of_Existence>
		<Method>
			<li>Finish specific research</li>
			<li>Combine all essence together</li>
		</Method>
	</Essence_Of_Existence>
	
	
	
</EssenceOfTheUniverse>
